{"level":"00000001","stage":"00000001","subject":"00000010","chapter":"00000184","totalQuestions":"12","canSkip":2,"minAttempt":"10","minPassingCriterea":"6","perStageMark":"1","skipedCount":0,"attemptedCount":0,"questionDetails":[{"questionId":"00003440","question":"Choose the correct answer: Proton","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16925","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016924":"Neutral#image#","0000016925":"Positive#image#","0000016926":"Negative#image#","0000016927":"Electric#image#","0000016928":"None of these#image#"}},{"questionId":"00003450","question":" _________ are the smallest complete units of matter.","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16975","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016974":"Molecules#image#","0000016975":"Atoms#image#","0000016976":"Protons#image#","0000016977":"Cells#image#","0000016978":"Substances#image#"}},{"questionId":"00003442","question":"Choose the correct answer: Thomson","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16936","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016934":"Scattering experiment#image#","0000016935":"Neutron#image#","0000016936":"Electrons#image#","0000016937":"Protons#image#","0000016938":"None of these#image#"}},{"questionId":"00003444","question":"Choose the correct answer: Iodine-131","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16948","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016944":"Isotope of chlorine#image#","0000016945":"Number of protons#image#","0000016946":"Nuclear fission#image#","0000016947":"Isotope of hydrogen#image#","0000016948":"Treatment of goitre#image#"}},{"questionId":"00003446","question":"Choose the correct answer: Atomic number","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16955","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016954":"Isotope of chlorine#image#","0000016955":"Number of protons#image#","0000016956":"Nuclear fission#image#","0000016957":"Isotope of hydrogen#image#","0000016958":"Treatment of goitre#image#"}},{"questionId":"00003441","question":"Choose the correct answer: Chadwick","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16930","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016929":"Scattering experiment#image#","0000016930":"Neutron#image#","0000016931":"Electrons#image#","0000016932":"Protons#image#","0000016933":"None of these#image#"}},{"questionId":"00003439","question":"Choose the correct answer: Neutron","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16919","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016919":"Neutral#image#","0000016920":"Positive#image#","0000016921":"Negative#image#","0000016922":"Electric#image#","0000016923":"None of these #image#"}},{"questionId":"00003438","question":"Choose the correct answer: Electron","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16916","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016914":"Neutral#image#","0000016915":"Positive#image#","0000016916":"Negative#image#","0000016917":"Electric#image#","0000016918":"None of these#image#"}},{"questionId":"00003449","question":"Choose the correct answer: Atomic mass","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":null,"correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016969":"Six electrons and 12 neutrons#image#","0000016970":"Six electrons and six neutrons#image#","0000016971":"Dalton#image#","0000016972":"Helium nucleus#image#","0000016973":"Protons and neutrons#image#"}},{"questionId":"00003448","question":"Choose the correct answer: Nucleus","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16968","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016964":"Six electrons and 12 neutrons#image#","0000016965":"Six electrons and six neutrons#image#","0000016966":"Dalton#image#","0000016967":"Helium nucleus#image#","0000016968":"Protons and neutrons#image#"}},{"questionId":"00003451","question":" ___________ is composed of molecules which are made up of atoms.","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16982","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016979":"Elements #image#","0000016980":"Substances #image#","0000016981":"Non-matter #image#","0000016982":"Matter#image#","0000016983":"Compounds #image#"}},{"questionId":"00003445","question":"Choose the correct answer: Uranium-235","questionimage":"","systemCorrectOptionID":"16951","correctOptionID":"NA","options":{"0000016949":"Isotope of chlorine#image#","0000016950":"Number of protons#image#","0000016951":"Nuclear fission#image#","0000016952":"Isotope of hydrogen#image#","0000016953":"Treatment of goitre#image#"}}]}